So, let us start with another video, in this video we will see the man in the middle attack
probably we will say M ITM, man in the middle, so then he made self with it, it was showing
someone's monitoring from middle of the network, before entering into the man in the
middle.
So, we need to understand the ARP protocol, so let us check for that, so first understand
about the ARP, so ARP stands for address resolution protocol, so you have an IP address ok,
but you need a MAC address to communicate into a network, so now this ARP help you to solve
this problem, so ARP will change, it will, it will ask the MAC address for the host into
the network ok, so that is why the name itself the address resolution protocol, resolving
the IP address into the MAC address ok, it will do the MAC address for you ok, so let us take
a router here, and we have a lot of machines inside the network that was connected into
the router, so outside of the network if you need to communicate outside to a network
so you can, the IP address is enough to communicate outside, but inside of a network for
some of this machine need to send high to this machine, so now this machine needs to know
the IP address of computer, let us think of the computer ABC, so computer A wants to communicate
it computer B, so computer A needs to know the IP address, sorry the MAC address of a computer
B ok, so the MAC address will be on of an important thing for communicate communication
inside the network ok, so by using the ARP protocol, so computer A will send a broadcast
recused to every host inside a network ok, so broadcast means it will be sent to everyone
inside the network ok, so computer will A will send like I have an IP, so let us think
of it computer AIP was dot 2, and computer B IP was dot 3, dot 3, let us own 92 160
dot 18 dot 3 ok, so the computer gave you last I have an IP, but I need a MAC for this
address, MAC for this address ok, the address is 18 dot 3, so it will send to every host
person inside the network if 100 computers are there, it will send to look 100 computers,
so let us think of it computer C has 18 dot 4, computer D has 18 dot 5, so now computer
C will reject I do not have the IP address of 18 dot 3, computer D will also reject because
I do not have the IP address of 18 dot 3 right, so now computer B will give the IP MAC
address to computer A ok, so computer B will give a MAC address to computer A ok, so now
computer A know the MAC address, because of the address resolution protocol ok, so more
time, so inside the network if you need to communicate we need a MAC address, so to resolve
the MAC address we need a ARP protocol, so ARP the computer A needs to communicate with
computer B, the computer will send a broadcast message to everyone inside the network,
computer A computer D computer D, so like I have an IP address of 18 dot 3, but I need
a MAC address of 18 dot 3, so it will be shared with everyone, so computer D do not have
the 18 dot 3 address, computer C also do not have 18 dot 3 address, computer B have 18 dot
3 address, so computer D will response to the computer A, I have an IP and my MAC address
is this ok, so now computer A and computer B can able to communicate with each other, so
they can enjoy the communication ok, so this is the overall explanation of address resolution
protocol, so let us think of it MATM, so here you have a router and here is your call
emission, so here is your Windows machine, so normal, a normal communication to what
the call emission and Windows machine will do call, Windows machine will send something
to router and router will send something to internet write, this is the normal communication,
so if use poisoned the ARP, ARP poisoning address resolution protocol poisoning, so now
what will happen, so let us think of it, here is your call emission and here is your
Windows machine, so you are tricking, you are doing some trick and you are saying to
you are saying, you are saying this Windows machine like, so I am the router ok, so now
Windows machine thing of it, so the calling machine is my router ok, so because you are
doing some optics ok, and you are saying I am the router ok, calling machine is the router
the attacker, the call is router and what Windows will now do, Windows will send all the
recused to the call emission and it got every response from the call emissions ok, so
once it send a recused to the call emission, call emission will send it to the router
and it will reach us to the internet ok, so you are doing some trick and you are saying
so I am the router ok, so send all the packets to me, I am the router send all the packets
to me, so now Windows machine will send all the packets to the call emission and call
emission transfer that packets to the internet ok, so I am not compromising this attack
because you can do it in terminal, so we can easily do it in GUI tool, so there is a lot
of ways to do, but I will say one of the easiest way you can do air piece poisoning
attack, so let me close off the previous OSR, we will clear this and we will stop the
service, stop the Apache service, let us pick on the Kali Linux logo and go to the sniffing
and the spoofing tool, so you can see the ether cap, so there is a GUI tool will be there,
also will be there, also you have a terminal based tool for a ether cap, so the easiest
one is a graphical user, so you can use the graphical user interface to do this attack
ok, let us open this, so now you got a console, primary it will be a constant, no need
to change, just assert this terms and condition, so now it was loaded, let me take my
primary machine and we will launch an attack, so my primary machine IP will be I/F config
so now you can find out 18.29 is my primary machine IP, that Windows machine IP, so this
machine okay, this machine IP was 18.29, so now let us scan the servers, so scan the host
person inside the network, so now you can find 18.29 and with the MAC address, if you
want to check the MAC address, I will show that I P config last R, now you can find
our physical address DC97DA, and similar ADZ97DA will be in the back, so now you can
become add to target, so now you can see the target get adder, now you go to the MATM menu
man in the middle attack menu, and you can see a lot of options will be there, they get
CP spoofing, stop MATM, and LDP poisoning, so we need the ARP spoofing, so I am selecting
the ARP spoofing here, so now we have successfully launched the ARP spoofing attack, right,
ARP poisoning attack, so now this Windows machine, this Windows machine will send all the
reduced to my calling machine, to my attack permission, okay, we will see that in next video,
we will try to login in one of the website, and we can see what happened if we do a ARP
poisoning attack, okay, let's swap off this video, and we will continue this video in the
next video, thank you, bye.